<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Collapsing Toolbar</string>
    <string name="contact_name">Razorshi </string>
    <string name="details">Software and Internet developers produce computer-based goods and services for individual consumers and companies. Software developers coordinate the production of software products, from choosing content providers, assembling graphics creators, and working with programmers, through the actual assembling, pressing and distribution of the final product. Internet producers go through much the same process, except instead of pressing a final product, they set up and maintain an Internet site that provides services to the user. Developers spend most of the day on the telephone coordinating production with the members of the team. One developer wrote that she sees herself as a chef: “The parts I have to put together are the ingredients, and I have to decide how and when to put them together to make a beautiful dish.” As pleasant as this sounds, developers are not strangers to hard work. Late nights are not unusual; unforeseen problems are standard. “Build in an extra two weeks to any project,” said one five-year software developer, “then you’ll only be two weeks late.” Software developers should be organized but flexible, and have strong technical and interpersonal skills. A high tolerance for frustration is equally important. Software and Internet producers are self-starters by nature and tend to tackle problems head on. Those who can combine all these talents will find themselves well suited to the industry. Developers told us the most exciting thing about the work is being able to produce a unique product that takes advantage of an unexploited medium. The final product each developer produces acts as a living resume, and many point with pride to the projects they are involved in. Also, because the software and Internet industries are so young, the field is wide open to those with talent. Talented developers are extremely mobile in this industry; ability sells, and many companies are willing to pay top dollar to have ability on their team. </string>
</resources>
